Oisín Tohak

Fullstack Developer

Email: <u>mail@oisintohak.com</u> Portfolio: <u>www.oisintohak.com</u> I'm an accomplished Fullstack developer with a keen eye for detail and design. I have a penchant for solving stubborn problems and am always eager to pick up new skills.

Skills

I have experience building web applications with HTML, CSS, JavaScript and Python (Flask). Providing an excellent user-experience while maintaining accessibility and responsiveness are always among my top priorities when building projects. For further details please refer to my portfolio.

Education

<u>Code Institute</u> / Diploma in Software Development SEPT 2020 - PRESENT, Ireland/Remote

I am currently completing the final module of this course.

<u>Galway Technical Institute</u> / FETAC Level 5 in Fine Art 2011 - 2012, Ireland

I received Distinctions in all 8 modules.

Experience

Govindas Galway / Catering

2012 - 2014, 2015 - 2021, Galway Ireland

I was involved in all aspects of running a successful Indian vegetarian food trailer. I was the sole operator for extended periods in which my duties included all preparation and cooking, sales and stock-keeping.

Oxfam / Fundraiser

2014, Dublin Ireland

I work with a team as a direct dialogue, door-to-door fundraiser. My main objectives were to inspire people to donate to the charity on a direct debit basis and to inform people about our humanitarian efforts.

References available on request.